前情提要
艾丽塔说十年后我就不在了
Aelita says I'm likely not to exist in ten years.
她这话什么意思?
What does she mean by that?
创伤是会留下痕迹的
The trauma leaves a mark.
我睡不着 躺在那里想着
When I can't sleep, I try to solve
怎么破解你和你妹妹的谜语
the riddle of your sister and you.
但我们只打算收养一个孩子
We were only planning to adopt one.
-那样的话... -沃尔夫不去 我也不去
- Well, perhaps in that case we could... - I'm not going without Wolf.
在你连接神经装置的时候 是什么感觉?
What's it feel like when you link up with your haptics?
如果你不把自己捋顺
It can kind of feel a lot like
你会有恋爱的感觉
love if you don't know any better.
有个笨蛋说你可能有活给我干
Some dumb fuck said you might have a job for me?
我有一杯敬酒和一杯罚酒
I've got a carrot, and I've got a stick.
我想再听听罚酒是什么
I'm curious about the stick.
下一枪就会打穿你的耳朵
Next one's in your fucking ear.
伦敦 2075年
嘿 沃尔夫 拿出来放在一起
Aye, Wolfy, oi, into the pot.
快
Come on.
就这些
That's it.
你是说 从自治市弄来的就这些?
So what you're telling me is that's it from the borough?
-奥马尔的手下抢先了一步 -你揩油了吧!
- Omar's crew got there first. - You nicked some, didn't you?!
-安格斯 住手! -你个该死的骗子!
- Angus, stop! - You damn liar!
- 小偷! - 安格斯 快走!
- You thief! - Angus, let go!
住手
Stop!
小偷!
Thief.
别做无用功了 安格斯 干点有用的
Quit mucking about, Angus. Get on with it.
你在干什么?
- What're you doing? - I'm being fair.
我很公平 他没赚到自己那份
- He ain't pulling his weight. - I'm pulling enough for him.
-我弄来的足够补他缺的 -那把你那份给他
Then give him your lot.
我不想要
I don't want it.
好啊 我给老鼠吃
Fine. I'll give it to the mouse.
然后会怎么样?
Then what will happen?
然后它会问你要点牛奶
Then... he'll ask for a splash of milk.
下一个!
Next in line!
那是什么?
What's that?
他们在派送免费食物
They're giving away free food.
靠不住吧
Dodgy, innit?
我从没见过这个地方
I never seen that place before.
你知道吗 沃尔夫?
You know what, Wolfy?
别吃了饭不干活
It's about time you earn your keep.
- 你去看看 - 他不能去
- Go have a look for us. - He's not doing that.
- 孩子们会被掳走的 - 抱歉
- Kids are getting snatched. - I'm sorry.
你需要女朋友保护你?
Do you need your girlfriend protecting you?
好孩子
Good lad.
市政府想清理街道
The city wants to clear the streets,
包括我们在内
and that includes us, too.
别犯傻 沃尔夫
Don't be stupid, Wolf.
你看到了吗?
You see that? You see that?
这会是我最后一次见你 沃尔夫
That's the last time I'll see you, Wolf.
我可不想被掳走
I'm not getting scooped.
沃尔夫!
Wolf!
一人限一个
Just one for everyone!
公共医疗卫生服务
艾丽塔!
Aelita!
沃尔夫!
Wolf!
- 艾丽塔! - 沃尔夫!
- Aelita! - Wolf!
艾丽塔!
Aelita!
- 沃尔夫! - 艾丽塔!
- Wolf! - Aelita!
沃尔夫!
Wolf!
艾丽塔!
Aelita!
一个植入物和两个化身的CPU?
An implant and two peripheral CPUs?
这就是艾丽塔留下的所有东西了?
This is all that's left of Aelita?
这也太让人苦恼了
This is all quite distressing.
我差点想把它们扔进河里
I'm half tempted to just dump these in the river
然后一切结束
and have done with it.
如果阿什和奥西恩能破解
Ash and Ossian should be able to trace
艾丽塔的植入物
where the Peripherals were piloted from.
他们就可以追踪 边缘人的所在地...
And if they can unlock Aelita's implant...
不一定行 因为有加密
Doubtful, given the encryption.
我们可以追踪其它线索
All I'm saying is there are other avenues for us to pursue.
但也留下了给别人追查的线索
And rather a few for others to pursue,
从尸体开始
starting with a corpse,
就算还没被发现 也很快就会被发现
which will be discovered soon, no doubt, if it hasn't already.
而且我们必须假设
And your DNA,
那个地方留下了你的DNA
we must presume, is scattered rather liberally
到处都是
all over the place.
我本会派人去清理那个地方
I would send a... team
但如果他们在那被发现...
to scrub the site, but if they were discovered there,
恩...
well...
至少做好准备
At the very least, you must gird yourself
艾丽塔可能已经死了
for the harsh reality of Aelita's death.
为什么?
Why?
没有植入物带来的免疫提升效果
Without the immunity boost of her implant,
她还能活多久?
how long could she last?
边缘世界
怎么搞的?
What the fuck?
弗林 我们有伴儿了
Flynne! We've got company.
什么风把你吹来了 汤米?
What's the word, Tommy?
过来看看
Oh, just thought I should come by.
打声招呼
Say hey.
我看到你在吉米酒吧
Saw you and Corbell Pickett shaking hands.
和科贝尔皮克特握手
Down at Jimmy's.
让我有点担心你
It had me a bit concerned.
这些废弃的车辆
All the abandoned vehicles.
那枚子弹
That bullet.
你放起的无人机
All them drones you got up.
我觉得应该过来看看
So, thought I'd come by for a visit.
我穿着普通人的衣服 开着普通人的车
My own clothes, my own truck.
好让你明白 我来这里是以朋友的身份
Just to make it clear, I'm here as a friend.
而不是副警长的身份
Not as a deputy.
很感谢 汤米
Appreciate that, Tommy.
感谢你的这番话 但是...
Everything you're saying, but,
唔...
uh...
你不用担心我们
you don't have to worry about us.
弗林 你怎么样?
What about you, Flynne?
还好吗?
You okay?
很好
Yeah.
我们都很好
Yeah, we both are.
那好吧
Well, all right, then.
该说的我都说了
Said what I had to.
你俩考虑一下吧
You two, uh, think on it maybe.
伯顿
And, uh, Burton?
记着
Try to remember...
我也是你们的朋友
the part about me being your friend?
看上去你需要朋友帮助
Look like you could use one.
我一定会的
I surely will.
我不喜欢这样 伯顿
I fucking hate it, Burton.
咱那样骗他, 我的意思是
Lying to him like that. I mean, I...
我装不下去了
I can't keep doing it.
咱们后面有十几具尸体
There's a dozen dead bodies out back.
汤米还不知道尸体的事
It's easy for Tommy to say he's our friend,
现在他当然会说是我们朋友
as long as he doesn't know about 'em.
一旦知道了
But as soon as he does,
他就会做回警察
he's also gonna remember he's a cop.
这是没办法的
There's no way around that.
为什么不能用 向其他人解释时用的说辞呢?
Why can't we just tell him what we're telling everyone else?
不能否认我们需要一些帮助
You can't really deny that we need some help right now.
我是担心你思路不清
I guess I'm worried you're not thinking clearly.
什么?
What?
你在这件事情上没法保持理性
You can't be rational about this.
你这是开我玩笑?
You fucking kidding me, right now? Rational?
-为什么 就因为我是女人? -我不是这意思
- Why? 'Cause I'm a woman? - That's not what I'm saying, Flynne.
不是所有人都像你和你战友那样冷血
Not everyone is as cold-blooded as you
以及你那些锅盖头朋友
and your fucking jarhead friends, all right?
没人想这样
Not everyone wants to be.
你在这事上牵扯太深
You're too tangled up in this.
什么牵扯?
Tangled up in what?
你在搜我丢的垃圾?
Have you been going through my fucking trash?
不用搜 就在最上面 弗林
It was right there, Flynne.
你给我滚
You need to leave.
马上滚出我的房间 伯顿
Get the fuck out of my room, Burton, now.
滚!
Go!
嘿!
Hey!
我知道你参加战争时受了很多痛苦
I know a lot of terrible shit happened to you off in the war.
我理解 我也很遗憾
I get that, and I fucking hate it.
但是参军是你自己选择的
But you went because you chose to.
在战争的阴暗面降临前 你有机会增长各种见识
And you got to see a whole lot of stuff
而我却不得不留在家里
before the bad stuff happened, okay, but I had to stay here.
爸爸去世后 是我支撑起了这个家
Okay, it was me who picked up the pieces after Dad died.
妈妈生病的时候 你回家的时候也一样
And when Mama got sick and then when your ass got home.
都是我 伯顿 都是我在操持
That was me, Burton! It was all fucking me!
-我什么都没有
And I didn't have nothing, Burton.
- 我知道 - 我什么也没有!
- I know it, Flynne. - I had nothing.
只有仿真游戏和一场傻傻的暗恋
I had nothing, just sims and a stupid fucking crush.
我知道这很傻 我不是白痴
And I know it's dumb, okay? I'm not an idiot.
-弗林 -但这对我很重要
- Flynne. - But it mattered to me.
因为这对我有帮助
- Flynne. Flynne! - It mattered to me because it fucking helped.
你没有资格
And you have no fucking right at all, no right
没有资格到我房间 跟我说那种话
to come in my room and say that shit to me!
弗林! 弗林?
Flynne. Flynne?
我的天!
Oh, fuck.
嗨！嗨！弗林?
Hey. Hey. Flynne?
莱昂!
Leon!
他应该更轻点吧?
Wasn't he a bit lighter?
肩膀应该更瘦削点
Thinner around the shoulders, I mean?
博士 我们用的是他最近的扫描
We used his most recent scan, Doctor,
七周前那次
from seven weeks ago.
也许当我们输入步态和姿态分析
Perhaps once we input gait and posture analysis,
他给人的整体印象就会不同
his gestalt impression will be different.
-我以为你已经这样做了 -还没有 但是...
- I assumed you'd already done that. - No, ma'am.
是的 拜托快去做吧
- But if you... - Yes. Please.
尽管去
By all means.
好多了
Mm, better.
说话
Speak.
型号X40927A
Model X409-27A.
为您效劳 女士
At your service, ma'am.
你输入过什么吗?
Have you input anything?
你之前要求保持系统空白的 博士
We were told you wanted a clean system, Doctor.
请进行语音扫描 开启自我意识
Voice scan and sense of self, please.
剩下的我来处理
I'll take care of the rest.
说话
Speak.
很高兴又见面了 努兰博士
It's nice to see you again,
音高有点过高了
- Dr. Nuland. - The pitch is rather high.
说话
Speak.
这符合您的记忆吗?
Does this fit your recollection?
后面我来
I'll handle it from here.
可怜的丹尼尔
Poor Daniel.
我不是含沙射影
No pun intended,
但当时的情形突然急转直下
but things did take a rather sharp turn
对于那是的我们，不是吗?
for us there, didn't they?
恐怕是的 女士
I'm afraid so, ma'am.
这是我们最新的型号 希望这能让你好受些
This is our most recent model, if that's any solace.
只有少量投入使用
There's only a few in service yet.
我觉得这可以看成是一种荣耀
I suppose one could see it as a sort of honor.
很高兴知道这一点 女士
I'm delighted to hear it, ma'am.
你有点太顺从了
Oh, no, you sound far too agreeable, though.
请调整一下
Um, adjust, please.
降低友好度
Decreasing amicability.
降多少比例?
By what percent?
降20%试试
Try 20.
如果这真是你想要的
If that's what you really want.
很好
Lovely.
那么...
Now...
你那天晚上不幸殒命
what do we have from your unfortunate encounter
我们从中有什么收获吗?
with mortality the other night?
威尔弗内瑟顿 被收养后
Wilf Netherton.
跟艾丽塔韦斯特成为兄妹
Adoptive brother to Aelita West.
列夫祖博夫的合伙人
Also known associate of Lev Zubov.
我们终于找到了盗窃组织的联系人
There's our Klept connection at last.
这样可能会让情况
Which would seem to rather unhappily
更加错综复杂
complicate the situation.
我一向尊重你的判断
I defer to your judgment, of course.
这点毫无疑问
Here and always.
不过在这件事情上 我有不同意见
Although in this particular case, I would tend to disagree.
你想杀了他们 是吧?
You want to kill him, don't you?
正是此意 博士
Oh, very much so, Doctor.
告诉我 在哪里可以找到列夫祖博夫
Tell me, where I can find Lev Zubov now?
扫描定位数据
Scanning localization data.
目标位置 弗吉尼亚沃特
Subject geolocated in Virginia Water.
紧急医护
这太愚蠢了 伯顿
This is stupid, Burton.
我感觉还好
- I feel fine.
20分钟前你糟透了
You didn't look fine 20 minutes ago.
- 现在也没好 - 我们应该保持低调
- You still don't. - I thought that we were supposed to stay quiet,
别人没必要知道的就别说
not tell people stuff they don't really need to know.
你突然抽风了 弗林
You had a fucking seizure, Flynne.
蒂拉安斯特德十年级的时候在化学课上
Tyra Ansted had a seizure in tenth grade, remember that?
癫痫发作 后来她就一直很好
In the middle of chemistry. Never happened to her again.
蒂拉安斯特德不用套上一个头戴设备
Tyra Ansted wasn't using a headset
去穿越到该死的未来
so she could travel to the fucking future.
这不是时间旅行 是数据传输
It's not time travel. It's data transfer.
她会告诉我 不要再戴那个该死的设备
And all she's gonna tell me is to not wear a fucking headset.
那我们就这么着
Then we'll deal with it.
- 怎么着? - 如果那个设备会伤害你
- How? - You're not putting on
就别戴 没得商量
the headset again if it's harming you, Flynne, period.
太可恶了
Goddamn it.
-你没事吧? -你居然问我这个?
- You okay? - Fucking seriously?
给我点空间行吗?
You just got to give me a little bit of fucking space, Burton.
-嘿 -怎么了?
- Hey, hey. - What?
迪迪在那里坐诊
- It's Dee Dee in there. - And?
-怎么了呢? -他是汤米的未婚妻，你觉得好吗？
And she's Tommy's fiancée. Are you cool with that?
我的天，你看上去...
Jesus Christ. I mean, it seems like you got...
你12岁的时候
Look, remember when you were 12 and you and Conner
你跟康纳把大麻藏在阁楼里 然后被我发现了 记得吗?
hid that fucking weed in the attic and I found it?
后来怎么样了?
What happened?
-我把它扔马桶里冲掉了 -然后你说什么?
- I flushed it down the toilet. - And said?
“咱永远不要提起这事”
- "Let's never talk about this again."
嗯哼，从那之后我今天是第一次提吧?
Uh-huh. This is the first time I brought it up since then.
你也别再提我暗恋汤米的事好吗?
Ain't it? How about you try doing that for me?
拜托?
Please?
跟你说句实话
Well, I'll be honest with you, Flynne,
这事情有点神秘
we have ourselves a bit of a mystery here.
根据伯顿的描述 你的情况像是
The way Burton is describing what happened makes it sound
典型的强直阵挛发作
like a classic tonic-clonic seizure.
他们以前叫“癫痫大发作”
What they used to call "grand mal."
如果真是那样 我应该可以
But if that were the case, I ought to be seeing
从脑电图上看到后遗症
the aftereffect on your EEG.
但我看不到
And I'm not.
脑电图看起来非常健康
This all looks perfectly healthy.
而且一般而言 强直阵挛发作后 会进入发作后阶段
Also a tonic-clonic is generally followed by a postictal phase--
昏睡 思路不清 失忆
deep sleep, confusion, amnesia-- but it sounds like
但是你发作之后就醒了 而且恢复了神智
you just popped up, more or less, and came on in.
生活里还发生了别的什么事吗?
Anything else going on in your life?
有什么新的或不同寻常的事?
New or out of the ordinary?
她在玩一个新款仿真游戏
She's been playing a new sim.
你是说虚拟现实?
- VR, you mean? - Uh...
比虚拟现实更精良
it's a little more elaborate than that.
是一种沉浸式体验
Sort of a full-body experience.
全新款头戴设备
- New sort of headset. - What's it called?
名字叫什么?
The new tech.
我指那新技术 我可以查查有没有相关研究
I can check and see if there have been any studies.
我觉得应该还没有名字
I don't believe it has a name yet.
哪里生产的?
Well, where's it from?
一家哥伦比亚的公司
Colombian company.
说来话长
It's kind of a long story, actually.
好的
Okay.
那就别再玩了
Well, stop using it.
用句你们玩家的行话
That seems like a no-brainer.
这不是什么“烧脑”的决定
To use a technical term.
我会对你的血液进行检查
I'll run your blood work, get you in for a CT scan
帮你在诊所约个CT扫描
at the Hefty Mart.
没问题
Sure.
与此同时 你要多休息
And in the meantime, rest,
多喝水 注意休养
fluids, all that good stuff.
如果出现异常就打电话给我
Call me if there's anything unusual.
我是说任何异常 好吗?
And by "anything," I mean anything.All right?
好的 迪迪
Sure thing, Dee Dee.
谢谢
Thank you.
伯顿 帮我个忙
Oh, and, Burton,
把你那家哥伦比亚公司的联系方式给我
will you do me a favor and send me the contact info
好吗?
for your Colombian company?
我要打电话问问他们头戴设备的事
I wanna call them about that headset.
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick or treat!
-我觉得她的意思是什么头戴设备都别用 -天哪
- I think she might've meant all headsets, Flynne. - Jesus.
有可能
Yeah, she might've meant all headsets,
但她没这么说
but she sure as hell didn't say that.
你打算怎么办呢?
What are you gonna do about that anyway?
她问我们要公司的名字
Her asking us what the name of the company is and all.
推拖拉呗
Dodge and delay.
有人觉得这是我最擅长的技巧
My most impressive skill set, some might argue.
我们不该告诉她的
I knew we shouldn't have told her.
她开那家诊所忙得很
She's got a lot coming at her, running that clinic.
过段时间肯定就忘了
Which'll do wonders to erode a person's attention span.
你在玩什么?
What are you playing?
没玩什么
Nothing actually.
在看
Just watching a...
我们家的视频
home movie.
哪部?
Which one?
很久以前拍的
One of the old ones.
我说
Hey, listen, uh...
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱歉什么?
For what?
你明天都要做脑部扫描了
You're getting a fucking brain scan.
道歉就从这件事开始
We can start there.
然后我们可以一直说
And then we can keep going, I imagine,
直到把需要道歉的事都说完
till I run out of things I need to apologize for.
但是 伯顿 妈妈的视觉恢复了
Yeah, but, Burton, Mama's seeing again.
那件事也要道歉?
Want to apologize for that, too?
我说的是对不起你的事 弗林
Talking about you here, Flynne.
我去过伦敦了 伯顿
I've been to London, Burton.
天哪 我去拜访了未来
Hell, I visited the future.
现在发生的一切不顺
None of the bad stuff happening right now...
都无法磨灭去未来所带来的感觉
...none of it can hold a candle to what it's like to go there.
你不知道这有多神奇
You have no idea how magical it is.
所以挺好的 不用担心
So it's fine, okay? Don't worry.
你也不用道歉
You don't need to say sorry.
我不是说你不应该这么做
I'm not saying you shouldn't do it.
如果你要做
But if you're gonna do it,
就得有个很好的理由
you better have a good argument for the doing it.
我说的好理由 不是说“我想看看那里是什么样的”
And by "good," I mean not just, "I want to see what it's like."
但我确实想看看那里是什么样的
But I do want to see what it's like.
我知道 我自己也会想去看看
I get that, and I wouldn't mind seeing myself,
但如果你也像弗林那样倒在地上
but we can't afford having you end up on your back,
口吐白沫 两脚乱蹬 我们可承受不了这个损失
kicking your heels against the floor and frothing at the mouth.
谁知道还会整什么幺蛾子出来...
Given the unknown contingencies we've been encountering
如果这东西确实伤害了弗林
- in the here and now. - If this shit is harming Flynne,
那就得有人去那儿
then someone's got to go there
找那帮混蛋算账
and knock those assholes back on their fucking heels.
你可以打电话给他们
I mean, they got these cool things called phones.
我是说亲自去 莱昂
I mean in person, Leon.
你这个说法欠点准确 不过意思我懂
I think that's the wrong way to put it,but I-I get what you're saying.
亲自上场 通过一个身体
Physically.In a body.
如果需要 就狠狠抽他们
Slamming up against theirs, if need be.
那个化身马上就可以登录 现在正是时候
She's scheduled any minute. Now's the time.
让这帮家伙吓一跳
Surprise the fucking shit out of 'em.
我并不想这样说，但说句不中听的
I hate to keep saying this cause it seems like you don't want to hear it,
如果你光荣负伤 我们就...
but if you end up WIA, we're all...
她登录进去之后 是有个身体的?
She's got a body when she goes in there?
真的身体?
A real one?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
抱歉什么?
For?
打扰了你
Disturbing you.
不可原谅吧?
Inexcusable, isn't it?
在我喝茶的时候打断我
Interrupting me whilst I sip my tea?
威尔弗 你的举止特像猫科动物
You have a strikingly feline manner
在屋子里悄么声的
slinking about the house, Wilf.
我一出现 你就会溜出房间
Always slipping out of rooms when I appear.
我直说 你老是这样溜走
I'll confess I always found it rather unappealing.
我感觉很没吸引力
Your constant slipping away.
这样显得你很狡猾
Seemed like a form of shiftiness,
不值得信任
as if you couldn't be trusted.
但有天晚上我和列夫屈尊
But then quite by chance, Lev and I went slumming it
去酒吧时
one night at SHUM.
很意外地看见你在那里跳舞
And we saw you there dancing.
然后我发觉 我认为的偷偷摸摸
And then I realized what I'd taken for sneaking about
实际上是一种舞蹈
was actually just a form of dancing.
是一种回避牵绊的方式
A way of skirting free from any entanglement.
因为这就是你害怕的东西 不是吗?
Because that's what you fear, isn't it?
你害怕被人牵绊
Someone getting hold of you?
不管是实际的 还是心灵上的牵绊
Literally or metaphorically?
跟我跳支舞
Dance with me.
你说什么?
I'm sorry?
迁就我一下吧
Indulge me.
就一会
Just for a moment.
然后我就不再折磨你了
And I'll stop tormenting you.
我保证
I promise.
♬ You can't read my mind ♬
♬  It's 4:00 a.m., I sashay with myself  ♬
♬  Couples all surround me  ♬
♬  So in love, eyes all aglow  ♬
♬ Oh, say you found me  ♬
♬ All my steps are memorized ♬
♬ Swaying to a rhythm so nice  ♬
♬  Patterns of my feet tattoo the floor  ♬
♬  They're frozen there like ice  ♬
♬  I dance with the ghost of you  ♬
♬  What else can I do ? ♬
对不起 我吓着你了吗?
So sorry. Did I startle you?
看来你对自己的周边监控
You obviously put a tad
有点太托大了
too much faith in your perimeter monitor.
能坐吗?
May I?
我一般不会不打招呼就过来
I wouldn't ordinarily drop by unannounced,
但我要抓住这次宝贵机会
but I wanted to grab a rare moment
跟你聊点私事 列夫
of privacy with you, Lev.
我能叫你列夫吗?
May I call you Lev?
我能叫你雪妮丝吗?
May I call you Cherise?
希望不要这么叫
I prefer not.
你从我这里偷了点东西
You stole something from me.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you mean.
艾丽塔韦斯特
Aelita West.
你付给她多少钱?
How much were you paying her?
如果有人理论上偷了你东西
If someone, theoretically, stole something.
一般的思路是 去警察局
One would think that you would go to the police.
除非 你根本不希望伦敦警视厅
Unless, you didn't want the Met to find out about this
把你理论上丢的东西给找到
theoretically stolen thing.
顺便问一句 你丢了什么呢?
What is it you're missing, by the way?
你瞧 你真会装糊涂
You see now, I'd accuse you of playing dumb,
不过你真是
but you seem to be forgetting
贵人多忘事
quite a bit of vital information recently,
你还忘了治理我们的实用政治
including the realpolitik that governs us all.
所以
So...
咱们快速复盘一下 行不行?
let's you and I have a quick review, shall we?
我们住在一座有三面墙的房子里
We live in a house with three walls.
盗窃组织的寡头统治集团
The Klept oligarchy,
通过运用极端暴力
through the application of extreme violence,
从世界末日的混乱中 建立了秩序
managed to bring order from the chaos of the Jackpot.
现在 作为回报 他们想追求利润
And now, in exchange for rather an open hand
希望有关部门睁一只眼闭一只眼
and blind eye when it comes to the free pursuit of profit,
这有助于维持那个秩序
it helps to maintain that order.
伦敦警视厅把盗窃组织的人
The Met Police keeps the Klept from straying beyond certain
控制在某个隐形的边界之外
implicit boundaries.
由此带来的和平与繁荣
The Research Institute
让研究所受益
benefits from the peace and prosperity that results,
同时也给社会带来技术支持
and in turn provides a technical assistance for society
促进社会运转和兴旺
to function and thrive.
这是我们造出的辉煌大厦
It's a wondrous edifice we've managed to construct.
但恐怕也非常脆弱
But it's also rather fragile, I'm afraid.
-那么屋顶是什么呢?
And what's the roof meant to be?
- 这是个隐喻 - 哦
- It's a metaphor. - Oh.
如果一面墙越过了自己本分
For the thing that will come crashing down on all of us
那么整个大厦就会坍塌 埋葬我们
should one of the walls overstep its bounds.
换句话说...
In other words...
就是世界末日 列夫
the end of the world, Lev.
亲爱的
- Oh, dear. - Mm.
你对盗窃组织的说法 有点不全面
Your description of the Klept left a bit out.
你说了 他们使用极端暴力
You mentioned the "application of extreme violence."
但世界末日那会 世界上充斥着暴力
There was no shortage of that in the Jackpot certainly.
但其他人失败了 盗窃组织依靠
But the Klept simply succeeded where others failed
隔代遗传的团结精神取得了成功
through a sort of atavistic tribal unity.
我们是一荣俱荣
Strike one of us, strike us all.
一损俱损
And suffer accordingly.
不过你说的这番话
I'm sure that you could express this all
确实比我的更有说服力
far more eloquently than I can,
还拿我的吐丝面包当道具
using my toast as a prop.
我刚才走过来的时候 你在看什么
What were you watching when I walked up?
我内人 你一定知道她是
My wife, as I'm sure you're aware,
佐洛托夫家族的
is a member of the Zolotov family.
你可能会说 盗窃组织中的顶级掠食者
Apex predators in the Klept world, you might say.
如果多米妮卡想要找家里的宠物玩
So if Dominika wishes to play with a family pet,
我凭什么质问她?
who am I to question her?
你是这样看内瑟顿先生的吗?
Is that how you view Mr. Netherton?
我很喜欢我的宠物
I'm rather fond of my pets.
比我朋友可靠得多
Far more reliable than my friends.
尤里萨姆索诺夫以前是你朋友
Yuri Samsonov was a friend once.
是吧?
Wasn't he?
可怜的尤里
Poor Yuri.
命运凄惨啊
Such a tragic fate.
但这个例子 跟这个
But also rather a relevant example
三面墙的房子有关系
in terms of our three-walled house.
你看 尤里萨姆索诺夫没守分
You see, Yuri Samsonov overstepped.
伦敦警察在研究所的技术支持下
The Met Police resolved the problem
解决了这个问题
with the technical assistance of the RI,
不过...
but...
恰恰是盗窃组织交出了尤里
it was the Klept who handed Yuri over.
是他曾经信任的人
Someone he trusted.
在脸颊亲了一下
A kiss to the cheek.
你知道研究所是怎么完成这个任务的?
Do you know how the RI accomplished the task?
我们对一群装配工做了调整
An assembler swarm.
让他们寻找萨姆索诺夫的DNA
Tweaked to seek out Samsonov DNA.
然后就把他整个家族给蚕食了
An entire lineage eaten away to nothing.
我可以感觉到你的想法 列夫
Your thoughts, Lev, I can... sense them.
你现在能吗?
Can you now?
我希望能
I hope so.
我希望你在想 “天哪 这个武器可真厉害”
I hope you're thinking, "My, what a powerful weapon.
这件武器在研究所放了这么多年了
And it's just been sitting in the RI all these years,
就是在等待下一个DNA样本
waiting for the next sample of DNA."
考虑一下吧 列夫
Think on that, Lev.
祝你愉快
Have a lovely day.
他在干什么 威尔弗?
What's he up to, Wilf?
不再躲躲闪闪了
No more dancing away.
你是做我盟友 还是敌人
Now you can be my ally here or my enemy.
自己选择
Your choice.
但我得说一句 做我的敌人
But I assure you it's not an easy path to walk,
日子可不好过
being my enemy.
弗林?
Flynne?
你是谁?
Who the fuck are you?
奥西恩 过来 马上!
Ossian, get up here. Now!
出了什么事?
What's happening?
该死的吵闹鬼
Fucking polts.
黑入了连接
Hacked the connection.
弗林?
- Flynne? - Friend of the brother's.
他哥的朋友 一只胳膊的
The triple amputee.
她往大门去了
Heading for the gates.
-怎么了 兄弟? -嘿 康纳
- You okay, buddy? - Hey, hey, Conner!
我们在这里 跟你在一起
- Conner? - We're with you, man.
我们在这里，你想要什么?
- We're right here. - What do you need?
告诉我们该怎么做
Tell us what to do.
送我回去
Send me back.
不给糖就捣蛋!
Trick or treat!
这是私人空间 内瑟顿先生
This is a private space, Mr. Netherton.
我没邀请你进来
I don't remember inviting you here.
我不知道...
I had no idea.
阿什安排了
Ash arranged it.
我很抱歉
I'm very sorry.
我想处理一些发生的事情
I wanted to address some issues that have arisen.
可以坐吗?
May I?
可以
Sure.
这是什么?
What is this?
家庭视频
It's a home movie.
我妈拍的
My mother filmed it.
有家公司把它做成了
There's a company that takes them
这个仿真游戏
and turns them into sims like this.
那是你?
That you?
我
Me,
伯顿
Burton,
还有我爸爸
and that's my dad.
-你爸穿着你的夹克? -不是
- Your father's wearing your jacket? - No.
我穿了他的
I'm wearing his.
感觉伯顿很像他
Burton looks like him.
对 伯顿还因此
Oh, yeah, and he is more
有点小自负
than a little bit conceited on that fact.
你生活的世界有一个文化特征
It's a cultural trait, I gather,
嘲笑你爱的人
from your part of the world, to mock the ones you love?
你凭什么觉得我爱他?
What makes you think that I love him?
你不爱?
You don't?
我当然爱
Of course I do.
他是我哥哥
It's my brother.
我愿意为他做任何事
I'd do anything for him.
你有兄弟姐妹吗?
Do you have any siblings?
有个妹妹
A sister.
那你多半能明白我的感受
Then I imagine you probably understand.
对了 出什么问题了?
So what are these issues that have arisen?
你朋友康纳拜访了我们
Your friend made a visit.Conner.
-什么? -是真的
- What? - It's true.
他用了你的化身
In your Peripheral.
他说你阵挛发作
He informed us of your seizure.
天哪
Fuck.
他觉得是头戴设备害的
Which he seems to believe the headset caused.
我猜你是来告诉我 不是头戴设备造成的
And I bet you're here to tell me it didn't.
我还不清楚
Well, I have no idea if it did.
这是我唯一一次十分确定
You know, that might be the only time that I'm...
你没在对我撒谎
100% sure that you didn't just lie to me.
好吧...
Well...
威尔弗雷德
Wilfred.
顺便说一句 我查了你的名字
I looked that up, by the way.
意思是“想要和平的人”
It means, "He who wants peace."
你知道吗?
You know that?
我还查了点其他东西
I looked some other stuff up, too.
没找到很多
Didn't find very much,
只找到我这个时代的列夫祖博夫
except a Lev Zubov. That exists in my time.
但我猜这名字在你老板的祖国很常见
But I imagine it's a common name where your boss comes from.
你发现了什么?
What did you find?
与黑手党相关的事
Mafia thing.
他、他的妻子、女儿、儿子
Him, his wife, his children,
都被杀了 是枪杀
daughters, sons, they were all murdered, shot.
房子被一把火给烧了
The house was set on fire.
非常可怕
Pretty gruesome stuff.
这跟你那的列夫没关系吧?
But no connection to your Lev?
完全没关系
- None at all. - Mm.
去做头部扫描
Get your scan.
我们会调查你的头戴设备
In the meantime, we'll investigate the headset.
如果情况安全我们才会叫你返回
We'll only ask you to return if it's safe.
我向你保证
I give you my word.
你还真喜欢作保证
You and your word, huh?
我是认真的
I mean it.
聊一次天居然说了两句真话
The truth twice in one conversation.
小心了 威尔弗 这会养成习惯哦
Be careful now, Wilf, it might become a habit.
还有一件事我没说
There's one thing I haven't shared.
艾丽塔
Aelita.
她是我的妹妹
She's my sister.
我是来见列夫祖博夫的
- Da? - I'm here to see Lev Zubov.
请把这个戴上 先生
Please put this on, sir.
这样做很有必要吗?
Was that absolutely necessary?
俱乐部有些上了年纪的会员
Some of the club's more elderly members
不喜欢被闯入者看见
don't take kindly to being glimpsed by interlopers.
你来这里是有充分理由的吧?
I take it you have good cause for this intrusion?
我...
I, um...
我见了我们的吵闹鬼
I met with our polt.
她说了些令人意想不到的消息
She shared some unexpected information.
在那个时间桩里 你的家庭
Y-Your family in the stub.
所有家亲眷属...
All of them.
他们都被人杀了
They were killed.
就在几周前
A few weeks ago.
手段残忍
Brutally.
不
No.
对不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
我
I-I... It's just that I can...
忘了你有多善良
forget how kind you actually are.
可能你也是
Maybe you do, too.
这让我有点替你担心
Makes me worry for you a bit.
坚硬的外壳下藏着柔软的心
That softness under the shell.
有人盯上他们了 列夫
Someone targeted them, Lev.
我猜就是这里的人
Someone from here, I presume.
你觉得我付钱给艾丽塔 是让她做什么?
What do you think I was paying Aelita to do for me?
我不知道
I have no idea.
你上次清楚表示
You made it quite clear that
这件事跟我没关系
you don't consider it any of my business.
我们想要学习如何打开属于自己的时间桩
We wanted to learn how to open a stub of our own.
盗窃组织为什么要打开时间桩?
- Why would the Klept want a stub? - Why would we want anything?
跟我们要其它东西的理由一样 因为有利可图
There's money to be made.
在时间桩中有利可图?怎么做到?
In a stub? How?
就看你脑洞够不够大
The only limit is one's imagination.
当然也看你的道德准则
And morals, I suppose.
举个例子?
For example?
我的兄弟阿列克谢 购买了一家制药企业
My brother Alexei purchased a pharmaceutical concern.
即便有人工智能
Even with AI, at some point,
他们还是需要 在一群人身上测试新药
one has to test a new drug on a human population.
出于医学道德
It's a process that medical ethics
整个过程很繁琐
could make rather tedious.
而且成本高昂
And costly.
所以你就去时间桩测试这种药?
So you tested it out in a stub?
我只是举一个例子
Yes, that's just a for instance.
我说过 可能性是
As I said, the possibilities are...
无限的
essentially infinite.
但有件事让我很困扰
But one thing troubled me, though.
在另一个世界有不同版本的我的想法...
The idea of different versions of myself in another world.
其存在虚无主义性
The existential nihilism of it.
我就是无法忍受
I just couldn't abide it.
你杀了自己的家人?
- You killed your family? - No, no, no.
当然不是我亲自干的
Not personally, no, of course not.
我汇了款 聘用了合适的人手干的
No, I transferred funds and hired the appropriate personnel.
可以告诉你 威尔弗
And I'll tell you something, Wilf.
我感觉好多了
I felt better.
立竿见影
Instantly.
实际上 如果我们能够
In fact, once we gain the ability
自己打开时间桩
to open these things ourselves,
我首先要做的就是这个
it'll always be the first task I'll address.
我本会提议把你的家族也清理掉
I would offer to take care of your lineage,
但是我发现你的家族谱系
but I realize your origins are a bit...
不太清晰
murkier.
还有什么想分享的吗?
Was there anything else you wanted to share?
没有了
No.
那就把眼睛蒙上
Better put that silly thing back on
离开吧
and be on your way.
奥斯瓦德老师呢?
What about, uh, Ms. Oswald?
佩里老师?特拉文廷老师?
Ms. Perry? Ms. Travantine?
教代数的佩里老师 还是教化学的佩里老师?
Algebra Ms. Perry or Chemistry Ms. Perry?
该死 我都忘了还有教化学的佩里老师
Shit. I forgot about Chemistry Ms. Perry.
没上过她的课 想不起她的样子
Never took her. Can't even picture her.
伯顿
Aw, shit, Burton.
决定跟谁做爱很简单 不是吗?
The "fuck" is easy, ain't it?
特拉文廷老师
Ms. Travantine, huh?
收到 天杀的
- Copy that. - Goddamn.
然后我选跟奥斯瓦德老师结婚
And then, I guess I'd marry Ms. Oswald.
她都有90岁了 哥们
She's like 90, man.
是的我知道，但是
Yeah, I know, but...
佩里老师是鼓励我入伍的人
Ms. Perry's the one who got me to join up.
她说如果我不参军会后悔的
Said I'd regret it if I didn't.
天哪
Chance to do
有机会做有意义的事 看看世界 一通瞎扯
some good, see the world, all that bullshit.
对我长篇大论
Gave me a whole fucking speech.
我以为那是你说的
I thought that was your speech.
对 我就是借鉴了她的
Yeah, I took it from her.
给你和其它傻帽一顿瞎掰掰
Gave it to you and those other fools.
她绝对是要“杀死”的那个
Okay. She's definitely the "kill."
有礼貌的人可能会敲门
A person with manners might knock.
你所谓的有礼貌的人可能会被
That same theoretical person might be a little scared off
你们在玩的超奇葩的游戏吓跑
by that weird-ass game you two were playing.
你该不会在听壁脚吧?
Probably wouldn't be eavesdropping, though,
不太确定...他们会不会粗鲁到偷听
- would she? - I'm not so sure they would not be rude enough
你们两个能闭嘴吗?
- to eavesdrop. - Would you two both shut the fuck up?
我的小请求
Please?
谢谢
Thank you.
你过来有事吗
Is there a reason you're here,
还是就想惹我发火?
or you just want to piss me off?
我其实是想听听你意见
I'm looking for advice, actually.
记得那个叫艾丽塔的女人吗?
You know this Aelita woman?
一开始就是她雇用我们的
The one that hired us in the first place.
我们终于找到了她住的地方
Well, we finally found out where she was living.
她那里有...
And she had this...
我们家房子的立体模型
this diorama thing of our house.
这辆旅行房车
This trailer.
还有你们大家
And of y'all.
你们的模型就像
Like these little...
玩具士兵
toy soldiers.
莱昂 里斯 卡洛斯 所有人 你们整个小队
Leon, Reece, Carlos. All of y'all. Your whole unit.
我在想 我想知道
So I guess I'm just wondering:
我到底该怎么办?
What the hell do I do with all that?
他们把头戴设备送来时
They said it was a sim.
说这就是个仿真游戏
When they sent the headset.
然后呢?
And?
没什么游戏是你搞不定的
Never saw one you couldn't master.
问题就在这 伯顿 这不是仿真游戏
That's the thing, Burton. This ain't just another sim.
但你之前以为是
But you thought it was.
如果你继续认为是游戏呢?
What if you kept thinking it?
就像康纳和他的棋盘一样
Like Conner with his chessboard.
他移动棋子 一切都转了起来
He makes these moves that set everything in motion.
你把这叫什么?
What do you call 'em?
开局策略
Gambit.
对 开局策略
Gambits, yep.
你的策略是什么呢 弗林?
What's your gambit, Flynne?
如果在仿真游戏中 你首先会怎么做?
What's the first thing you do when you get in a sim?
打破脚本
Break script.
与他们的预判反着来
Do the exact opposite of what's expected.
会发生什么?
And what happens?
会牺牲很多条命
I die a bunch.
看上去会很傻
Look pretty stupid.
然后呢?
And then?
我搞清楚所有规则
I figure out the rule set.
然后
And then?
获得主动
I take control.
这就对了
Fuck yeah.
冰易 咱就这么干吧
Easy Ice.Let's do that.
你和我 上线登录
You and me go in there.
然后开始死
Start dying.
别落下我 这次绝不能
Not without me, motherfuckers, not this time.
上阵的人越多
More boots we got on the ground,
被击败的可能性就越低
the less likely we are to get our asses kicked in there.
这只是基本战术
That's just basic tactics, ain't it?
满嘴跑火车 你只是想上线去看看
You are so full of shit, Burton. You just want to see it.
是又怎么样?
And what if I do?
这不重要
Besides, it doesn't matter
除非你阵挛发作好透了 否则不能上
'cause you're not going back in there till we get your seizure sorted out.
已经好透了
It's all sorted.
看到扫描结果后我们才能确定
It ain't sorted till we see the scan.
我感觉挺好的
I feel fine.
我想要回去 伯顿 好吗?我得回去
I want to go back, Burton. Okay? I need to.
你打电话给梅肯和爱德华
So you go on ahead and call Macon and Edward.
我们没时间耗下去
It's not like we got time to waste.
下一波追杀我们的人 还有多久会找上门?
How long do you think it's gonna be till someone else comes around wanting to kill us?
- 你手怎么样了? - 正常了
- How's your hand? - Everything's back to normal.
我告诉你了
Okay? I told you.
我会帮你们弄到身体的
I'll get you bodies.
你们俩都会有
Both of you.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
你父亲呢?
Where's your father?
弗林?
Flynne? The children.
孩子们 进屋去 马上
Inside. Now.
我不在这里的时候 就是个玩具?
Am I being used as a toy when I'm not here?
他们需要四个人才能玩
They needed a fourth.
感觉又无伤大雅 我很抱歉
It seemed harmless enough, but I apologize.
你来干什么?
What are you doing here?
做一个身体要多久?
How long does it take to make
干嘛?
- one of these? - Why?
我要两个 一个给康纳 一个给伯顿
'Cause I need one. For Conner. Another one for Burton, too.
你上哪去?
Where are you going?
仿真游戏玩家往往有专长
You see, sim jockeys tend to have a specialty.
有成就型 探索型 杀手型
Achievers, Explorers, Killers.
我是探索型的 阿什 我觉得该是开始探索的时候了
I'm an Explorer, Ash, so I think now's a pretty good time to start.
切断她的连接
- Cut her connection. - Working on it, luv.
正在切断 亲爱的 但那些吵闹鬼在阻止我
But the polts are countering.
感觉他们相当熟练
Rather adeptly, I'm afraid.
-她要走了 -最好跟着 你觉得呢?
- She's leaving. - Best follow, don't you think?
祖博夫在哪里?
Where in the bloody hell is Zubov?
不管他在哪 听到吵闹鬼在瞎转悠 他总不会高兴
Wherever he is, he won't be happy to hear our polt's gone a'wandering.
如果伦敦警方再跟她邂逅一次
If the Met Police encounter her again,
她这次小探索就会让我们完蛋
this could be the end of us.
我是说咱们所有人 亲爱的
And I mean all of us, luv.
去通知他
Alert him.
你这举动很无脑哎 弗林
This is really quite stupid, Flynne.
如果你想参观参观 我可以...
If you want a tour of the city, I can happily...
看一些你事先安排好的东西? 不必了 谢谢
Show me exactly what you want me to see? No, thank you.
那样就不是探索了 对吧?
That's not really exploring, now, is it?
能不能解释一下 你这次探索的目的是什么?
Maybe you can explain the point of this exploring.
看那些你没给我看过的东西
I want to see all the shit you haven't been showing me.
我保证 都给你看了...
I assure you, there is absolutely nothing...
说话的时候看着我的眼睛
Damn it, look me in the eye when you say it.
我想看看你当面扯谎时的表情
I want to see the expression you make when you lie to my face.
打扰了 祖博夫先生
Apologies for the interruption, Mr. Zubov,
现在情况变得有点紧急
but we have a situation that is turning somewhat urgent.
那个吵闹鬼没事先安排就突然上线
The polt has made an unscheduled visit.
我们可能需要内瑟顿先生的帮助
Mr. Netherton's assistance may be in order.
我这就派他过去
I'll send him straight there.
恐怕不是派到这里 目前直接派到帕丁顿会更好
Not here, I'm afraid. More-more toward Paddington at the moment.
有点没法确定位置
Though this appears to be rather fluid.
该死的 切断她的连接 奥西恩
Oh, for fuck's sake, Ossian, cut her connection.
好的 先生 这个主意很妙
Aye, sir. Brilliant idea.
我们正在努力切断
And-and-and we're working on it, but in the, in the meantime,
与此同时 你能不能派内瑟顿先生过来帮忙
if you could just dispatch Mr. Netherton...
你这个该死的大笨蛋!
Oh, you fucking prat!
不是说你 先生
Not you, sir.
-你不需要那样做 -我需要
- You don't need to do that. - Yes I do, Edward.
你把事情复杂化了 别让他靠近就行
You're overcomplicating this as usual.
我知道黑客大战怎么打 我从没败过
You just got to keep him at bay.  I'm aware how a hacker battle works, okay? I never lost.
-让开 -你不知道怎么做
Move. Move.  No, man, you don't know what to do.
让开
Get out my way.
如果你直接告诉我...
If you simply tell me...
艾丽塔告诉我 我大概只能再活十年 阿什
Aelita told me I'm likely to die in ten years, Ash.
你觉得她这话什么意思?
What do you think she meant by that?
大家都在哪里?
And where are all the people?
断开了?
Done?
有没有听到我胜利的呐喊响彻屋宇?
Did you not hear my roar of victory echoing across the rooftops?
“不惜一切代价夺取胜利 不惧一切恐怖...”
"Victory at all costs. Victory in spite of the..."
回到祖博夫家
Return to the Zubov residence.
要不...
What about...?
不好
No, no, no, no, no, no.
伯顿 让她闭上眼睛
Hey, Burton? Yeah. Tell her to shut her eyes.
闭眼
Shut them now!
这下三滥的家伙
- That sneaky little prick. - Come on, move, move out of the way.
-让开 -等等 我能行
- What? Wait, I got to...
我就说你会搞砸
Come on, I told you you'd fuck this up.
又回来了是吧?
Back again, are we?
人都去哪儿了 阿什?
What happened to the people, Ash?
你确定就是这里?
You're certain this is the place?
奥西恩说在这里 走进大门 右转
According to Ossian. Head through the gate and bear right.
我们称这是“中大奖”
We call it the Jackpot.
不是一件事 而是很多事同时发生引起的
It wasn't one thing. Or all at once.
所有的事加在一起
It was everything together.
随着时间愈演愈烈
Building over time.
就算到现在 他们还在争论这到底是什么时候发生的
Even now, they're still arguing about when it technically began.
已经开始了吗?在我的时代?
It's started, though? Already in my time?
是的
Yes.
真会挑地方散步
Nice place for a stroll.
她有权知道 内瑟顿先生
She has a right to know, Mr. Netherton.
道德权利
A moral right.
把代码发给我
Send me the damn code.
这是什么?
What is this?
我们的过去 你的未来
Our past, your future.
类似于博物馆
A museum of sorts.
不同形状代表世界末日的不同阶段
Each of these shapes represents a different phase of the Jackpot.
为什么说是中大奖?
Why "the Jackpot"?
我觉得算是黑色幽默吧
Gallows humor, I suppose.
没有“世界末日”听起来那么可怕
And it's less portentous than "Apocalypse."
人们普遍把这个时刻认定为临界点
This is the moment commonly pinpointed as the edge of the cliff.
在这之后 世界一泻千里 末日之势无法阻挡
After which there is no turning back. The Jackpot was unstoppable.
针对北美电网的黑客攻击
A hack of the North American electrical grid.
造成全面停电
Complete blackout.
长达数月 遍及整个北美洲
Monthslong, continent-wide.
结果发现 这是一种在全球范围内
An increasingly common phenomenon, as it turned out.
越来越普遍的现象
Across the globe.
2039年
距离我的年代只差七年
That's just seven years off in my world.
疫病大流行
Pandemic.
线状病毒
A filovirus.
我们叫做“血之瘟疫” 它攻击内脏
We called it the Blood Plague. It attacked the viscera.
血液充满在肝脏、脾脏、肠子 直到肚腹涨破
The liver, spleen, intestines filling with blood till the abdomen burst.
2041年
环境灾难
Environmental catastrophe.
干旱 饥饿 抗生素失效
Droughts. Famine. Antibiotic failure.
随后是农业大减产
Agricultural collapse followed.
人口锐减
Full population collapse.
四十年左右有70亿人死去
Bit more than seven billion people. Over four decades or so.
然后该阶段结束
And then came the end.
美国遭遇国内恐怖分子袭击
A domestic terrorist attack in the United States.
他们引爆了核弹发射井
They blew up a nuclear missile silo.
北卡罗来纳州 斯普林克里克
Spring Creek, North Carolina.
我的上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
我就住在那里
That's where I live.
快停下!
Geez, just make it stop.
你还好吗?
You okay?
给我们弄到身体了吗?
You get us bodies?
还在弄
I'm working on it.
下集预告
你相信有些时刻 命运会来到岔路口吗?
There are moments when fate can go one way or another.
情况完全可能比现在糟得多
Thousand ways it could have gone wrong back there.
不能沉湎于过去
Can't dwell on the past, Flynne.
在那个秘密的地道里
What mysteries do you oversee,
巨大的铁门后面 你负责什么神秘的事?
down there in your secret burrow with the big steel door?
现在要保密是很难了
It's getting real hard to keep this under wraps.
我开始信任你了
I'm starting to trust you.
我错了吗?
Is that a mistake?